(Leonard:)Butterfly could've
gotten himself
(Leonard:)home from Arizona.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I feel renewed.
(Sheldon:)I'm ready
(Sheldon:)to deal with any changes
(Sheldon:)that come my way.
Hey!
Look who's back!
(Penny:)Your hair is different.
You changed your hair.
(Sheldon:)I can't take this.
I'm out.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to see pictures
from my trip?
(Penny:)I thought your
phone got stolen.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, it did,
but luckily all my photos
(Sheldon:)got backed up to the Cloud.
(Leonard:)And you thought they
all had a silver lining.
(Sheldon:)Here... day one.
(Sheldon:)Uh, this was the seat
(Sheldon:)I was going to sit in but didn't
(Sheldon:)because there were
cracker crumbs on it.
(Sheldon:)As it was first class,
I suspect Ritz.
(Sheldon:)This is the train bathroom.
(Sheldon:)This is the Imodium I took
(Sheldon:)so I would never have
to use the train bathroom.
(Penny:)I cannot believe
you traveled the
entire country
(Leonard:)and never left
the train station.
(Sheldon:)I know.
You know, I almost died
(Sheldon:)in a fire in Des Moines,
but I stayed put.
(Sheldon:)FYI...
(Sheldon:)That's when
the Imodium gave out.